Stephen Jay Gould Papers, 1899-2004
Stanford University Libraries.
- Series 7. Columbia University
  - Paper - Geology of Felton Hill, Sudbury, Vermont (Box 658, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts and research proposals (Box 696, Folder 10)
- Series 8. Harvard University
  Gould taught at Harvard University from 1967 until his death in 2002. This series contains teaching materials and course files Gould compiled and assembled throughout this period, as well as administrative and departmental files amassed and created during the course of his career.
  This series has been arranged into three subseries:
  Teaching materials and course related files. Files are listed by course title. Highlights include syllabi, exams, lecture notes, and research materials. Represented are some of Gould's most notable courses including Science B-16, "The History of the Earth and Life," and the "Thinking about Thinking" classes, which were often taught with friend and colleague Professor of Law Alan M. Dershowitz, as well as other notable Harvard thinkers. Also included is student coursework without identifying student numbers or grades.
  Administrative, departmental, and other Harvard related files. Files include routine departmental correspondence and faculty related memoranda, event invitations, death notice cards, and regular Harvard publications such as directories, yearbooks, and other departmental pamphlets.
  Student Work. Contains course files with student numbers and/or graded coursework. It is closed for research until 2086.
  - Subseries 1. Teaching materials and course related files
    - Biology 17 (2 folders)
    - Biology 17, 1991-1992 (Box 605, Folder 4)
    - Biology 17, 1993 (Box 605, Folder 5)
    - Biology 17, 1994 (Box 605, Folder 6)
    - Biology 17, 1995 (Box 605, Folder 7)
    - Biology 17, 1999 (Box 605, Folder 8)
    - Biology 17, notes (Box 914, Folder 7)
    - Biology 106 (Box 914, Folder 8)
    - Biology 208, 1988-1989 (Box 914, Folder 9)
    - Biology 208, 1990 (Box 914, Folder 10)
    - Biology 208, 2000 (Box 914, Folder 11)
    - Biology 208 - Animal Origins (Box 607, Folder 6)
    - Biology 208 - Course reading list and topics (Box 542, Folder 6)
    - Biology 208 - Mass Extinctions, 1995 (Box 542, Folder 7)
    - Biology 246 (Box 542, Folder 8)
    - Biology 246, 1978 (Box 914, Folder 12)
    - Biology 246, 1980 (Box 914, Folder 13)
    - Biology 246 - Schedule, syllabus, class roster (Box 543, Folder 10)
    - Biology 248 (Box 605, Folder 9)
    - Biology 248, 1968-1971 (Box 914, Folder 14)
    - Biology 248, 1976-1977 (Box 914, Folder 15)
    - Biology 248, 1978 (Box 607, Folder 7)
    - Biology 248 - Chaisson - Scenario of Cosmic Evolution (Box 543, Folder 14)
    - Biology 248 - Evolutionarily Stable Strategies (Box 543, Folder 11)
    - Biology 248 - Evolutionarily Stable Strategies (c.2) (Box 543, Folder 12)
    - Biology 248 - Hierarchical Linear Modeling (c.1-c.3) (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - Biology 248 - Mass Extinction (c.1) (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - Biology 248 - Mass Extinction (c.2) (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - Biology 248 - Modes of Animal Speciation (Box 543, Folder 15)
    - Biology 248 - New Evolutionary Law; Pattern and the Balance of Nature (Box 543, Folder 13)
    - Biology 248 - Phylogeny of Prokaryotes, pt.1 (Box 543, Folder 5)
    - Biology 248 - Phylogeny of Prokaryotes, pt.2 (Box 543, Folder 6)
    - Biology 248 - Probabilistic Models in Evolution (c.2) (Box 543, Folder 7)
    - Biology 248 - Punctuated Equilibria (c.2, c.3) (Box 543, Folder 4)
    - Biology 248 - Origins of the Nucleate Organisms (Box 543, Folder 8)
    - Biology 248 - Origin of nuclei and of eukaryotic cells (Box 543, Folder 9)
    - Biology 248 - Sexual Dimorphism (Box 542, Folder 9)
    - Biology 248 - Sexual Dimorphism and Niche Utilization (Box 542, Folder 10)
    - G 151, 1967-1971 (Box 915, Folder 1)
    - G 151 - Discussion bibliography (Box 914, Folder 21)
    - G 151 - Handouts (Box 914, Folder 22)
    - Geology 18, 1971-1973 (Box 914, Folder 16)
    - Geology 141, 1971 (Box 914, Folder 17)
    - Geology 141, 1974-1981 (Box 914, Folder 18)
    - Geology 141, 1976-1977 (Box 914, Folder 20)
    - Geology 141 - Invertebrate Paleontology - Lab manual, Fall, 1975 (Box 914, Folder 19)
    - Geology 180 (Box 915, Folder 2)
    - Geology 202 (Box 915, Folder 3)
    - Geology 202 (Box 915, Folder 3)
    - Geology 206 (Paleontology), course reserves (Box 605, Folder 10)
    - Geology 241 (Box 915, Folder 4)
    - Geology 241 - Handouts, 1979 (Box 915, Folder 5)
    - Geology 241 Course Reserves (2 folders)
    - Geology 257, 1968 (Box 915, Folder 6)
    - History of Paleontology (Box 543, Folder 18)
    - History of Paleontology, 1975 (Box 543, Folder 17)
    - History of Paleontology, Spring, 1975 (Box 543, Folder 16)
    - History of Science 132 (4 folders)
    - History of Science 132 (2 folders)
    - History of Science 132 - Beringer, Lying Stones (Box 543, Folder 27)
    - History of Science 132 - Course readings (Box 544, Folder 3)
    - History of Science 132 - Course readings (2 folders)
    - History of Science 132 - Course readings (3 folders)
    - History of Science 132 - Course reserves (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - History of Science 132 - Eternal metaphors of... (Box 543, Folder 23)
    - History of Science 132 - Eternal metaphors of... (Box 543, Folder 26)
    - History of Science 132 - Hutton, Theory of the Earth, c.1 (Box 544, Folder 4)
    - History of Science 132 - Hutton, Theory of the Earth, c.2 (Box 544, Folder 5)
    - History of Science 132 - Rudwick, The Meaning of Fossils (Box 543, Folder 28)
    - History of Science 132 - Rudwick, The Meaning of Fossils, Chapter 4 (Box 543, Folder 29)
    - History of Science 132 - Rudwick, The Meaning of Fossils, Chapter 3 (Box 544, Folder 1)
    - History of Science 132 - Rudwick, The Meaning of Fossils, Chapter 5 (Box 544, Folder 2)
    - History of Science 132: Theories of the Earth (Box 915, Folder 7)
    - History of Sciecne 232 (Box 915, Folder 8)
    - History of Science 232, 1987 (Box 915, Folder 9)
    - History of Science 232: Evolution and Cognition (Box 915, Folder 10)
    - Natural Sciences 10, 1972-1973 (Box 915, Folder 12)
    - Natural Sciences 10, 1975-1976 (Box 915, Folder 13)
    - Natural Sciences 10, 1978 (Box 915, Folder 14)
    - Natural Sciences 10 - First term lecture (Box 915, Folder 11)
    - Natural Sciences 10 - Syllabi, 1965-1970 (Box 915, Folder 15)
    - Natural Sciences 10 - Syllabi, 1970-1975 (Box 916, Folder 1)
    - Natural Sciences 36 (2 folders)
    - Philosophy 192 coursepack, 1996 (Box 545, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, 1991 (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, 1993-1994 (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, Spring, 1994 (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, 1996 (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, 2000 (Box 916, Folder 4)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, 2000 (Box 606, Folder 6)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, notes (Box 606, Folder 7)
    - Philosophy 192 - Thinking About Thinking, reserve materials (Box 606, Folder 8)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking (Box 545, Folder 10)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking (Box 607, Folder 8)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking, 2002 (Box 607, Folder 9)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking, coursepack (Box 546, Folder 1)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking, coursepack (volume 3) (Box 546, Folder 2)
    - Religion 1045 - Thinking About Thinking, course packet, 2002 (Box 607, Folder 10)
    - Science B16 (Box 545, Folder 5)
    - Science B-16 (2 folders) (Box 697, Folder 1-2)
    - Science B-16 (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - Science B-16 (Box 916, Folder 6)
    - Science B-16, 1981-1982 (Box 916, Folder 7)
    - Science B-16, 1985-1993 (Box 916, Folder 9)
    - Science B-16, 1988-1989 (Box 916, Folder 11)
    - Science B-16, 1991 (Box 606, Folder 9)
    - Science B-16, 1992 (Box 606, Folder 10)
    - Science B-16, 1992-1993 (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - Science B-16, 1994 (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Science B-16, 1996 (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - Science B-16, 1996 (Box 916, Folder 10)
    - Science B-16, 2000 (Box 916, Folder 12)
    - Science B-16, 2000-2001 (Box 916, Folder 13)
    - Science B-16, 2002 (Box 916, Folder 14)
    - Science B-16, course evaluations, 1992 (Box 606, Folder 11)
    - Science B16 - Coursepack (Box 545, Folder 6)
    - Science B16 - The History of Life (Box 545, Folder 7)
    - Science B16 - The History of Life, midterm exam, 1996 Mar 15 (Box 545, Folder 8)
    - Science B-16 - Lab, 1981 (Box 916, Folder 8)
    - Science B-16, notes (Box 916, Folder 5)
    - Science B-16, readings (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - Science B-16, reserve articles, Tomlinson (2 folders)
    - Science B16 - Time (Box 545, Folder 9)
    - Core curriculum (Box 547, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (about courses) (Box 547, Folder 3)
    - Course Evaluation Guide, 1994-1995 (Box 547, Folder 6)
    - Course readings (2 folders)
    - Course readings (6 folders)
    - Course readings and notes (Box 604, Folder 1)
    - Course reserves, miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 605, Folder 1-3)
    - Course reserves, miscellaneous (5 folders) (Box 604, Folder 1-6)
    - Course reserves, miscellaneous (Box 541, Folder 13)
    - Courses (Box 547, Folder 2)
    - Exam materials (Box 547, Folder 4)
    - Extension - Exams, schedules, handouts (Box 914, Folder 4)
    - Reading list for lecture by A. C. Wilson, 1980 Mar 17 (Box 547, Folder 7)
    - Reprints for course reserves (miscellaneous) (3 folders)
    - Reprints for course reserves (miscellaneous) (Box 547, Folder 1)
    - Student work - Biology 17, 1996 (Box 916, Folder 15)
    - Student work - Biology 17, 1998 (Box 916, Folder 16)
    - Student work - Biology 17, 1999 (Box 916, Folder 17)
    - Student work - Biology 208, 1994 (Box 916, Folder 18)
    - Student work - Biology 248, 1972-1973 (Box 917, Folder 1)
    - Student work - Biology 248, 1974 (Box 917, Folder 2)
    - Student work - Biology 250, 1968 (Box 917, Folder 3)
    - Student work - Biology 321, 1979 (Box 917, Folder 4)
    - Student work - Biometrics papers (3 folders)
    - Student work - Geology 141, 1971 (Box 917, Folder 5)
    - Student work - Geology 241, 1974 (Box 917, Folder 6)
    - Student work - Geology 241, 1975 (Box 917, Folder 7)
    - Student work - Geology 241, 1976 (Box 917, Folder 8)
    - Student work - Geology 241, 1976 (Box 917, Folder 9)
    - Student work - Geology 241, Undated (Box 917, Folder 10)
    - Student work - Harvard EPS Admit List, 2002 (Box 918, Folder 8)
    - Student work - History of Science 132r, 1977 (Box 917, Folder 11)
    - Student work - History of Science 132r, Undated (Box 917, Folder 12)
    - Student work - History of Science 211r, 1978 (Box 917, Folder 13)
    - Student work - Natural Sciecnes 10, 1971 (Box 917, Folder 14)
    - Student work - Philosophy 192, 1990 (Box 917, Folder 15)
    - Student work - Science B-16, 1981 (Box 918, Folder 1)
    - Student work - Science B-16, 1990 (Box 918, Folder 2)
    - Student work - Science B-16, 1992 (Box 918, Folder 3)
    - Student work - Science B-16, 1993 (Box 918, Folder 4)
    - Student work - Miscellaneous course evaluations (Box 918, Folder 9)
    - Student work - Miscellaneous papers (Box 918, Folder 10)
    - Student work - Miscellaneous papers (2 folders)
  - Subseries 2. Administrative, departmental, and other Harvard related files
    - Academic calendar (Box 547, Folder 8)
    - Administrative (Box 547, Folder 9)
    - Administrative correspondence (Box 547, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action Handbook (Box 547, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Carol Services, 2000 (Box 547, Folder 12)
    - Harvard Computing Center (Box 547, Folder 13)
    - Conference and symposia material (Box 547, Folder 14)
    - Core Review Committee, 1997 (Box 547, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 547, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 548, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 548, Folder 2)
    - Courses of Instruction Supplement, Fall 1995-96 (Box 548, Folder 3)
    - Daily notes for Gould, prepared by Agnes Pilot, 2000-2001 (Box 548, Folder 4)
    - Death notice cards (2 folders)
    - Department of Geological Sciences (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Doctoral Theses in Geology, Mineralogy, Geophysics and Geography (Box 548, Folder 8)
    - Enrollment Guide, 1995 (Box 548, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Activities, Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 548, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council elections (Box 548, Folder 11)
    - Faculty information (Box 548, Folder 12)
    - Faculty meetings (Box 548, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Research Working Paper Series (Box 548, Folder 14)
    - Faculty, staff and student directories (Box 549, Folder 1)
    - Flyers (Box 549, Folder 2)
    - Earth History and Paleobiology at Harvard (Box 549, Folder 3)
    - Events (Box 549, Folder 4)
    - Funeral service programs (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Grade distribution (Box 549, Folder 6)
    - Harvard Monthly Expense Report for November 1995 (Box 549, Folder 7)
    - Human rights (Box 549, Folder 8)
    - Incoming letters from colleagues and faculty (Box 549, Folder 9)
    - Introduction to Core Curriculum - A Guide for Freshmen (Box 549, Folder 10)
    - Office supply receipts and requisition forms (Box 549, Folder 11)
    - Organismic and Evolutionary Biology (Box 549, Folder 12)
    - Organismic and Evolutionary Biology - Graduate studies (Box 549, Folder 13)
    - Professional development pamphlets (Box 549, Folder 14)
    - Publications (Box 549, Folder 16)
    - Publications (Box 550, Folder 1)
    - Report of the Committee to Visit the Museum of Comparative Zoology (Box 550, Folder 2)
    - Report of the University Science Policy Committee (Box 550, Folder 3)
    - Rules of Faculty Procedure, 1997-1998 (Box 549, Folder 15)
    - Sexual harassment information (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Songs of Harvard (Box 550, Folder 5)
    - Sponsored Accounting Manual (Box 550, Folder 6)
    - State of the Faculty Report, 2001 (Box 550, Folder 7)
    - Student handbooks (2 folders)
    - Students with Disabilities at Harvard (Box 550, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (2 folders)
    - Kermit/CMS, MS-DOS (Box 550, Folder 13)
    - Watchdog (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - USDA - Permit information (Box 551, Folder 2)
    - Right to Know (health hazard information) (Box 551, Folder 3)
    - The demise of Agnes' 286 computer (Box 551, Folder 4)
    - Gateway 2000 = 486 DX (Box 551, Folder 5)
    - HP LaserJet series II printer (Box 551, Folder 6)
    - Main frame account (Box 551, Folder 7)
    - Computer purchases (Box 551, Folder 8)
    - Ned era: computer receipts (Box 551, Folder 9)
    - Digitizer Panazonic Video (Box 551, Folder 10)
    - Chorus Data Systems (Box 551, Folder 11)
    - BMDP Software - 88.2 upgrade (Box 551, Folder 12)
    - Computer Misc. (Dave's) (Box 551, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and records - Computer purchase, 1989 (Box 551, Folder 14)
    - PC's Limited/Dell 286 computer in RM118 (Box 551, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 551, Folder 16)
    - Handbooks and other publications (Box 551, Folder 17)
    - Death Notice Cards (Box 551, Folder 18)
    - Harvard Paleo-Biologists, Holiday Cards (Box 607, Folder 11)
    - Yearbook - 337, 1973 (Box 690, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (4 folders), 1992-2002 (Box 697, Folder 3-6)
    - Death Notice Cards (Box 697, Folder 7)
    - Department of Geology (Box 697, Folder 8)
    - Environment at Harvard, 1997-1998 (Box 697, Folder 9)
    - Handbook on Race Relations and the Common Pursuit, 1997 (Box 697, Folder 10)
    - Invitations (Box 697, Folder 11)
    - Publications (miscellaneous) (Box 697, Folder 12)
    - OEB (Box 697, Folder 13)
    - Directories (Box 697, Folder 14)
    - Event announcements (Box 697, Folder 15)
    - Gould's identification cards (Box 697, Folder 16)
    - Stationery (2 folders) (Box 697, Folder 17-18)
    - Harvard, 1967-1969 (Box 914, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 914, Folder 2)
    - Request for Financial Support for the Acquisition of an Image Analysis System for the Department of Invertebrate Paleontology, Museum of Comparative Zoology, Harvard University (Box 914, Folder 3)
- Series 9. New York University
  Gould served as a visiting professor at New York University from 1996 until his death in 2002. This series contains administrative material, correspondence, and departmental publications from this period.
  Course files with student numbers and/or graded coursework are closed for research until 2086.
  - Administrative (Box 682, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1995-2002 (Box 682, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2002 (Box 682, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 682, Folder 4)
  - Directory, 1999 (Box 682, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Student Handbook (Box 682, Folder 6)
  - Lecture Schedule (Box 682, Folder 7)
  - Open Enrollment (Box 682, Folder 8)
  - Principles of Biology, 2001 (Box 682, Folder 9)
  - Publications (Box 682, Folder 10)
  - Reading Darwin - Freshman Seminar (Box 682, Folder 11)
- Series 10. Organizations, committees, boards
  Gould was the recipient of many prestigious fellowships throughout his career and served on numerous committees and boards. He was a longtime fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, the American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), the National Academy of Sciences (NAS), and the Royal Society of Edinburgh. In 1981 Gould was among the first group of recipients of the MacArthur Foundation Prize fellowship. He served in officer and advisor capacities on numerous boards for organizations such as the Bermuda Biological Station, the Rockefeller Foundation, and the Smithsonian Institution. Files in this series are listed in alphabetical order by organization.
  Records containing sensitive nomination and election materials are closed for research until 2086.
  Note: there is some overlap between this series and the Subject Files series, where a significant number of files related to these organizations and committees also exist.
  - 3-2-1 Contact Advisory Committee (3 folders)
  - American Academy of Achievement (Box 501, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 501, Folder 2)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 678, Folder 9)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (2 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) (5 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) (3 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) (Box 501, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) (2 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) (2 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1983 (Box 919, Folder 6)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1997 (Box 919, Folder 7)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - 1982 talks - Draft [c?] what happened ev (Box 919, Folder 5)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Advisory Committee for International Science - "Welcome to International Programs..." (Box 501, Folder 4)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition, 1998 (Box 501, Folder 5)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition (2 folders), 1999
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition, 2000 (Box 501, Folder 8)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition, 2000 (Box 678, Folder 10)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition (2 folders), 2000
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition, 2001 (Box 678, Folder 11)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual Meeting and Science Innovation Exposition, 2002 (Box 552, Folder 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual meetings
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Annual reports (Box 502, Folder 5)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Art and science [s?] (Box 919, Folder 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Awards (Box 502, Folder 6)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Baseball, 2000 (Box 919, Folder 10)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Board of Directors, 1997-1998 (Box 502, Folder 7)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Board of Directors (2 folders), 1998
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Board of Directors (2 folders), 1998-1999
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 502, Folder 12)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Committee on Scientific Freedom and Responsibility - Should There Be an Oath fro Scientists and Enginneers? (Box 502, Folder 13)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Committee on Scientific Freedom and Responsibility - Turning a Blind Eye? (Box 503, Folder 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Correspondence (4 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Council (Box 919, Folder 11)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Council meetings (Box 503, Folder 6)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Directorates (Box 503, Folder 7)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Directory of Human Rights and Resources on the Internet (Box 503, Folder 8)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Election 2000 (Box 503, Folder 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Evolution and Ethics (Box 919, Folder 12)
  - American Association for the Advancemnet of Science (AAAS) - Evolution and Ethics (Box 922, Folder 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Finances (Box 503, Folder 10)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Fellowships (Box 503, Folder 11)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - First Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2001 (Box 504, Folder 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Founders' Day Lecture (Box 504, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 504, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) and teaching evolution (2 folders)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Handbooks - Officers Organization Activities 97/98, 1997-1998 (Box 504, Folder 6)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Handbooks - Officers Organization Activities 98/99, 1998-1999 (Box 504, Folder 7)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Human Rights and Health (Box 504, Folder 8)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Losing Ground (Box 504, Folder 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Membership demographics (Box 504, Folder 10)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Minutes (Box 922, Folder 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) - Miscellaneous (Box 504, Folder 11)